maxmouth.com 2008-06-10

# MaxMouth

| 

Recently Added

Most Viewed

Highest Rated

Popular Tags

| 

_Last Updated July 25, 2007_

MaxMouth, Inc. ("MaxMouth") recognizes that its users who use www.MaxMouth.com or other web sites owned or operated by Maxmouth (the "MaxMouth Sites") (collectively or individually "Users") value their privacy. This privacy policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the MaxMouth Sites. By using the MaxMouth Sites, you consent to the collection and use of your information by us in accordance with this privacy policy.  If we update or modify this privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you will always have the ability to know what information we collect, how we use the information, and under what circumstances we deliver the information.  Your continued use of the MaxMouth Site after any changes are posted constitutes your acceptance of the new terms. This privacy policy is incorporated into and is subject to the MaxMouth Terms of Use. Your use of the MaxMouth Sites and any personal information you provide on the MaxMouth Sites remains subject to the terms of this privacy policy and our Terms of Use.

Please note that any video, image, or other content posted onto the MaxMouth Sites becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this policy.

## The Information MaxMouth Collects

  * User Provided Information: You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to MaxMouth when choosing to participate in various activities on the MaxMouth Sites such as creating an account to be a Registered User, uploading videos, posting messages in our forums or in the video comments section, entering contests or sweepstakes, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists. 
  * Cookies Information: When you visit the MaxMouth Sites, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. MaxMouth uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the MaxMouth Sites may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. 
  * Log File Information: When you use the MaxMouth Sites, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 
  * Clear GIFs Information: When you use the MaxMouth Sites, we may employ "clear GIFs" (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our Users anonymously (i.e., in a non-personally-identifiable manner). In addition, we may also use clear GIFs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. 

##  How MaxMouth Uses Information

  * Any personally identifiable information is voluntarily provided to us.  If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the MaxMouth Sites, then we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the MaxMouth Sites and as otherwise described below. 
  * Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (e.g. on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you upload videos, post comments, or vote through the MaxMouth Sites and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. Any videos that you submit to the MaxMouth Sites may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels via the embedded player functionality described in the Terms of Use, and may be viewed by the general public. 
  * We may use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages  to you.  You have the ability to choose whether or not to receive these message through your user account that you create when you become a Registered User (or that you subsequently modify or update). We may also use your email address non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major MaxMouth Site changes or for customer service purposes). 
  * We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, click stream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the MaxMouth Sites and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends. 
  * We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the MaxMouth Sites; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; and (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc. 

##  When MaxMouth Discloses Information

  * We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our privacy policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 
  * From time to time we may share your profile information to carefully selected companies whose products and services may be of interest to you.
  * We share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the MaxMouth Sites. 
  * We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant. 
  * MaxMouth also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that MaxMouth believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our web site, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of MaxMouth, our Users or others. 

## Your Choices

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the MaxMouth Sites, in which case MaxMouth you may not be able to access all of the services MaxMouth has available to you. You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your account profile page. Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites 

MaxMouth permits other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the MaxMouth Sites. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the MaxMouth Sites. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.  
MaxMouth does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks . However, please note that if an advertiser asks MaxMouth to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement by clicking the ad, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the MaxMouth Sites that they collect by virtue of you clicking through on an ad,(such as the number of times you viewed an ad), to determine which ads to deliver to you.  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks  for more information on their practices. MaxMouth's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

## Our Commitment to Data Security

MaxMouth uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to MaxMouth and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, MaxMouth makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

If MaxMouth learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you as required by law so that you can take appropriate protective steps. 

To protect your privacy and security, we use industry standard security technologies and we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times.  You should contact us immediately at [Privacy@maxmouth.com](mailto:Privacy@maxmouth.com) if you believe your account information or your password has been compromised.

## We Are Committed To Children’s' Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, MaxMouth does not knowingly collect or maintain any information on the MaxMouth Sites from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the MaxMouth Sites at any time or in any manner. If MaxMouth learns that personally identifiable information of persons less than 13 years of age has been collected on the MaxMouth Sites without verified parental consent, then MaxMouth will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

## Special Note to International Users

The MaxMouth Sites are hosted in the United States and are intended for and directed to Users in the United States. If you are a User accessing the MaxMouth Sites from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the MaxMouth Sites, which are governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Notice, and our Terms of Use, you are voluntarily transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer and any additional transfers that may subsequently take place.

## If there is an Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy

In the event that MaxMouth is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

## Contact Information

Please contact MaxMouth with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice using this contact form. <http://www.maxmouth.com/contact.php>

| 

MaxMouth video- click to view videos  
  
---|---|---
